[Music]
icici lombard and cnbc tv 18 present
india risk management awards risk master
class
if the way in which you look at an
insurance company was always a risk
transfer
you know uh institution but over the
last four or five years we have made an
attempt to actually shift the entire
focus from
just being a risk transfer mechanism to
actually becoming a risk partner
and developing solutions for corporate
clients uh wherein the risk itself can
you know reduce so over the years if i
if i just categorize the
risk you know it could be property it
would be supply chain it could be health
and liability
and each in each of these segments you
know we have come out with certain
solutions which would
you know help the clients reduce their
business risk as well as operational
risk
icici lombard and cnbc tv 18
present india risk management awards
risk master class